Hello. Metro Garage.
Can I help you?
>> I don't think you're supposed to answer
that.
>> Hello.
Hi.
>> [music and singing]
>> Yes? Hi.
How are you?
Is this Wilson?
>> [laughter]
>> She's answering [music] phone calls over
here.
>> Bye.
Hi. I [music] used to have
>> I got
>> I did it as a joke.
>> Bye girls. Have the best last day at
school.
Bye.
Bye George. Bye pig.
So long. Thanks for my ride to work.
>> Okay. Five stars.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey Casey. If you film all these shots
yourself, how do you get those tracking
shots where you're moving through
camera? Funny you should ask. See that?
See my office window up there?
That little camera right there. The
little white one.
So that little thing tracks me and then
I control it with with this remote
control. And I can like it auto tracks
me it tracks me automatically and then I
can actually control the camera.
The camera's some seriously futuristic
All right. Do we go?
Yeah.
>> [music]
>> Jordan and I are going on a quick lunch
break mission to do something I've
always wanted to do [music] but I've
never never done before. What does this
car do?
What are you doing?
Connecticut plates.
It's a secret subway station mission.
6 train.
>> 6 train.
>> [music]
>> Here's the mission.
New York City's most beautiful subway
station is one very few New Yorkers have
seen. Here's how you get there that's
illegal but free. Okay, take the 6 train
downtown. That's what we're doing right
now. When the train makes it to its
final stop, passengers are told to exit
the train. Stay on the train and duck
down so you're not easily spotted.
>> All right, everybody off at South Ferry.
South Ferry. Last stop. No more
passengers. This is the last stop on
this train. No more passengers. Last
stop.
>> Oh, I guess
Where is it going?
Okay, this is it. We did it. That was
way easier than I thought.
Let me try to make make this make sense.
When the New York City Subway first
opened on October 27th, 1904,
it was the magnificent City [music] Hall
Loop Station
with its arched Guastavino tiled
ceilings and skylights that served as
the centerpiece
for the opening [music] festivities.
But by 1945, the new longer subway cars
could no longer fit on the curved
station's tracks
and that station was closed forever.
Now, for whatever reason,
the 6 train still goes around that
curve. You don't to take the four, you
don't want to take the five, you got to
take the six. Not the four train, not
the five train. Four, five, and six all
are on the same line, but only the six
train. And it stops at the very last
station before the loop station.
>> It's a mad stop on this train.
>> Then it goes through that loop station,
comes back around the other side,
everybody gets back on and goes in the
other direction. So, if you stay [music]
on,
you can like get a glimpse of that old
station.
>> Do you see it?
>> I don't see it yet. I don't know which
which window it's out of.
>> This is it!
The train stopped.
>> Why did we stop?
Why did we stop?
We're just going to go back and do the
ride again.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Oh,
All right, what's for lunch?
>> [music]
[music]
>> How about we do a little quest?
>> Yeah.
>> A secret.
This is my gear room.
This is my gear.
The The gear room is not the secret. The
secret is that I never use
any of this stuff.
My favorite thing in the whole world is
[music]
making little videos and making them by
myself. Like I'm with my friends, but
I'm making the video by myself. And for
these videos, like my YouTube my little
YouTube videos, my favorite ingredient
is spontaneity. Like I see something
interesting and I'm like, "Oh, I can
make a video about that." That's why I
carry this goofy camera on my hip. So,
when I see my wife answering the phone
at a parking garage, I can like I can
grab that little clip. That's fun.
That's spontaneous.
>> I don't think you're supposed to answer
that.
>> Hello.
>> The challenge is how do you maximize the
cinematography? So, visually it's it's
it's interesting without interrupting
the spontaneity of what you're
capturing. The goal is always minimal
camera gear that lets me do everything I
need to do. This is the whole kit. It
fits in half a backpack. I have main
camera, tiny tripod, zoom lens, action
cam, 360 cam, tiny drone, selfie stick.
That's the kit. That's the maximum
spontaneity, minimal setup. That's the
whole kit, but there are limitations to
that. One in particular I've never been
able to figure out is how do you get a
zoom camera like this to follow you
without having to have another person
with a zoom lens set up somewhere to get
that like panning shot. And that's why
this little cute Wally-looking camera is
now officially part of my kit. And the
stabilization is so good. This is a
video I made like last week.
I shot a lot of this on the Luna Ultra.
Like that's on the Luna Ultra. That's on
the Luna Ultra. And then there's one
shot in particular, right? That shot.
Do you know how hard it is to get a shot
a stabilized tracking shot of a
of a poodle with a tennis ball in her
mouth? That was all in the the Luna
Ultra.
>> [music]
[bell]
>> Wait, there's one very important detail
about the secret subway tunnel thing.
Hey, let me ask you something.
>> Uh-huh.
>> When people stay on they go see the old
abandoned
train stop? You know what I'm talking
about?
>> were allowed to ride this train through
the loop and they can observe the uh the
old city hall.
>> you're allowed to do it now?
>> Yes, you're allowed to do it.
>> Not illegal at all.
>> Also, I watch your vlogs all the time.
>> I appreciate it.
>> [music]
[music]